

Profile

I am a highly motivated worker, who likes to face new challenges. I learned Chinese and English by myself and got into Chinese University. Also while getting my degree I have got into a Chinese-Ukrainian Pharmacology company and signed 47 successful contracts.

I had done my own research about testing and I decided to take QA courses at Hillel school. It helped me to gain the knowledge to work confidently on projects, which I am willing to use in a company that will provide me with the chance to learn and develop myself as a Software Tester.

Employment History

International Relationships Department at pharmaceutical company Highwell, Kyiv, Ukraine

August 2020 — February 2022

- Signed 47 deals with major Chinese Pharmaceutical companies.
- Held meetings with representatives from China for further cooperation.
- Responsible for the purchase, transportation of medical goods to the territory of Ukraine.

Manager at Roomin Shanghai, Shanghai, China

December 2018 — January 2020

- Cooperation with foreign clients, assistance with documents in China.
- Assistance to a foreigner in the selection of housing and preparation of all necessary documents.

Education

Bachelor Degree, Donghua University, Shanghai, China

September 2018 — Present

Bachelor in Business and Chinese language

Courses

QA manual, Hillel School

March 2022 — July 2022

★ Certificates

HSK 5

IELTS

Details

+1 (929) 425-6840 annshter@gmail.com

Links

GitHub

Skills

Postman

JIRA

GitHub

Jmeter

Test plans

Test cases, check list

Load testing

Regression testing

Acceptance testing

Agile and Scrum

HTML & CSS

SQL

Languages

English

Russian

Ukrainian

Chinese